{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 1,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "We know Earth is not ___________.", "answer": "flat" },
        {
          "prompt": "Sid deposited cash in the ___________.",
          "answer": "cash"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She plays the trumpet in the ___________.",
          "answer": "band"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Class begins when the ___________ rings.",
          "answer": "bell"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I know I ___________ my coat on the chair.",
          "answer": "left"
        },
        { "prompt": "Get the book on the top ___________.", "answer": "shelf" },
        {
          "prompt": "The lottery brought her ___________.",
          "answer": "wealth"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The losing players had ___________ faces.",
          "answer": "grim"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ grinds wheat into flour.",
          "answer": "mill"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If he can’t guess the answer, I’ll give him a ___________.",
          "answer": "hint"
        },
        { "prompt": "The story had an amazing ___________.", "answer": "plot" },
        { "prompt": "Tie the sailboat to the ___________.", "answer": "dock" },
        { "prompt": "___________ the stain with a towel.", "answer": "blot" },
        {
          "prompt": "Is three an ___________ or even number?",
          "answer": "odd"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ of two plus two is four.",
          "answer": "sum"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ripe ___________ fell off the tree.",
          "answer": "plum"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you really run faster than him, or is that just a ___________?",
          "answer": "bluff"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Some birds can ___________ hard seeds.",
          "answer": "crunch"
        },
        { "prompt": "How do you ___________ a birdhouse?", "answer": "build" },
        { "prompt": "We played soccer in ___________ class.", "answer": "gym" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Her dad was a ___________ in the army.",
          "answer": "major"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Myra made a ___________ pot in art class.",
          "answer": "clay"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Our family took in a ___________ kitten.",
          "answer": "stray"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The special for ___________ is meatloaf.",
          "answer": "today"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use a bucket to ___________ out the water.",
          "answer": "bail"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The fence ___________ needed to be fixed.",
          "answer": "rail"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ was clogged with peas.",
          "answer": "drain"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I heard a ___________ scratching sound.",
          "answer": "faint"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "They ___________ to make the best pie.",
          "answer": "claim"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The baby bird was a ___________ pink color.",
          "answer": "pale"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She has the cutest little ___________!",
          "answer": "face"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The sheep ___________ in the pasture.",
          "answer": "graze"
        },
        { "prompt": "The woman leaned on her ___________.", "answer": "cane" },
        { "prompt": "I wrote in chalk on a ___________.", "answer": "slate" },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ in her ankle worsened.",
          "answer": "ache"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I prefer a ___________ over a burger.",
          "answer": "steak"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I wonder what else she will ___________!",
          "answer": "break"
        },
        { "prompt": "Today my sister turns ___________.", "answer": "eight" },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ all sat down to watch their favorite show.",
          "answer": "they"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "You must ___________ the doctor’s orders.",
          "answer": "obey"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "It was a cold, moonless ___________.",
          "answer": "evening"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ had a lot of stripes.",
          "answer": "zebra"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "People can’t ___________ under water.",
          "answer": "breathe"
        },
        { "prompt": "I joined the baseball ___________.", "answer": "league" },
        {
          "prompt": "That door was loud and ___________.",
          "answer": "squeaky"
        },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ bandaged the cut.", "answer": "healer" },
        { "prompt": "That’s a ___________ new car.", "answer": "sleek" },
        {
          "prompt": "Wet floors are very slippery ___________!",
          "answer": "indeed"
        },
        { "prompt": "We can’t fish near the ___________.", "answer": "reef" },
        { "prompt": "Are you sorry for that ___________?", "answer": "deed" },
        { "prompt": "Did you listen to the ___________?", "answer": "speech" },
        { "prompt": "The runner started to ___________.", "answer": "wheeze" },
        {
          "prompt": "The sidewalk is made of ___________.",
          "answer": "concrete"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Your ___________ needs more planning.",
          "answer": "scheme"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Kevin thinks it is beyond ___________.",
          "answer": "belief"
        },
        { "prompt": "Who is the ___________ here?", "answer": "chief" },
        { "prompt": "Do you want ___________ in your tea?", "answer": "honey" },
        {
          "prompt": "This ___________ will carry our tent.",
          "answer": "donkey"
        },
        { "prompt": "Let’s go home to your ___________.", "answer": "family" },
        { "prompt": "I am too ___________ to play.", "answer": "weary" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "She started to ___________ the rock wall.",
          "answer": "climb"
        },
        { "prompt": "I was ___________ my own business.", "answer": "minding" },
        { "prompt": "She baked two blueberry ___________.", "answer": "pies" },
        {
          "prompt": "Water the rose, or it will ___________.",
          "answer": "die"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Amy measured the door’s ___________.",
          "answer": "height"
        },
        { "prompt": "She gave a ___________ as she waited.", "answer": "sign" },
        { "prompt": "The movie gave us a ___________.", "answer": "fright" },
        { "prompt": "The baby had a ___________ fever.", "answer": "slight" },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you know how to ___________ a car?",
          "answer": "drive"
        },
        { "prompt": "Please use a ___________ cabinet.", "answer": "file" },
        {
          "prompt": "It is a perfect day to fly a ___________.",
          "answer": "kite"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "October is the ___________ month to see fall colors.",
          "answer": "prime"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "He carried the flag with ___________.",
          "answer": "pride"
        },
        { "prompt": "Carlos cut a slice of ___________.", "answer": "slice" },
        {
          "prompt": "We only went to the pool ___________.",
          "answer": "twice"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use a rag to ___________ up that spill.",
          "answer": "wipe"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use a screwdriver to ___________ it open.",
          "answer": "pry"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The three ___________ pigs tricked the wolf.",
          "answer": "sly"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ toddler hid in his room.",
          "answer": "shy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The detective will ___________ on the thief.",
          "answer": "spy"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ of lightning lit up the sky.",
          "answer": "bolt"
        },
        { "prompt": "The old bread had ___________ on it.", "answer": "mold" },
        {
          "prompt": "We pay a ___________ to cross the bridge.",
          "answer": "toll"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ moved with the light.",
          "answer": "shadow"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I love to watch the river ___________ by.",
          "answer": "flow"
        },
        { "prompt": "Dana ___________ the lawn each week.", "answer": "mows" },
        {
          "prompt": "Is that picture ___________ on the wall?",
          "answer": "lower"
        },
        { "prompt": "Wind had ___________ the chair over.", "answer": "blown" },
        { "prompt": "Do you know a famous ___________?", "answer": "quote" },
        { "prompt": "A ___________ dug holes in our yard.", "answer": "mole" },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ is large and smooth.", "answer": "stone" },
        { "prompt": "Ana cooked beans on the ___________.", "answer": "stove" },
        {
          "prompt": "Each team captain ___________ a player.",
          "answer": "chose"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I have gum on the ___________ of my shoe!",
          "answer": "sole"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A raccoon ___________ eggs from the farm.",
          "answer": "stole"
        },
        { "prompt": "Lucie scored the winning ___________.", "answer": "goal" },
        {
          "prompt": "I ___________ every time that happens!",
          "answer": "groan"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The computer program takes time to ___________.",
          "answer": "load"
        },
        { "prompt": "Mom is ___________ a turkey.", "answer": "roasting" },
        { "prompt": "“___________ is me,” the actor moaned.", "answer": "woe" }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
